Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - Composers Da-Dela [1953-1985] (Box 36)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Dachalier, 2.Daetwyler, 3.Dagincourt, 4.Dahl, 5.Dalcroze, 6.Dale, 7.Dalza, 8.Damase, 9.Dameron, 10.Damett (EMPTY), 11.Damrosch, L., 12.Dandrieu, J.F., 13.Dandrieu, P., 14.Danyel, J., 15.Dankworth, 16.Danzi, 17.Daquin, 18.Dargomijsky (EMPTY), 19.Dasar, 20.Daugherty, 21.Dauvergne, 22.David, F., 23.David, G., 24.David, J.N., 25.Davidovsky, 26.Davies, P.M., 27.Davis, A., 28.Davison, J.W., 29.Dawson, 30.Deak, 31.Deason Dates of materials: 1953, 1966, 1978, 1985
  - Composers Deli-Dom [1960-1985] (Box 36)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Dederkind, 2.De Koven, 3.De Kruyf, 4.De La Barres, 5.Delage, 6.Delande, 7.De Lamarter, 8.De La Torre, 9.De La Vega, 10.De Lavigne, 11.De Leeuw, 12.De Leone, 13.Dellario, 14.Demantius, 15.Dembski, 16.Denis, 17.Denison, 18.Dennis, B., 19.Dennis, J., 20.Dennis, R., 21.Dering, 22.De Sabata, 23.De Sayve, 24.Des Molins, 25.Dessau, 26.Destouches, 27.Dett, 28.De Vate, 29.Devienne, 30.De Vise, 31.De Voto, 32.Diabelli, 33.Diamond, 34.Di Capua, 35.Dick, M., 36.Diepenbrock, 37.Dietrich, 38.Dillon, 39.Di Pasquale, 40.Diruta, 41.Dissevelt, 42.Distler, 43.Dittersdorf, 44.Divitis, 45.Dlugorai, 46.Dodge, 47.Dohnanyi, 48.Dolphy, 49.Dominicus de Feraria Dates of materials: 1960, 1971, 1982, 1985
  - Composers Don-Dz [1953-1984] (Box 36)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Donatoni, 2.Donovan, R., 3.Dorati, 4.Dorman, 5.Dorsam, 6.Dougherty, 7.Douglas, W., 8.Downey, 9.Downing, 10.Draghi, 11.Dragon, 12.Dragonetti, 13.Dresher, 14.Drew, J., 15.Drew, L., 16.Drigo, 17.Driscoll, 18.Drury, R., 19.Druschetzky, 20.Dubensky, A., 21.Dubois, 22.Du Caurroy, 23.Ducasse, 24.Duckworth, 25.Dueben, 26.Duff, A.K., 27.Duffy, 28.Dufrene, 29.Duke, 30.Dukelsky, 31.Du Mage, 32.Dumont, 33.Duni, 34.Duparc, 35.Duphly, 36.Duport (EMPTY), 37.Dup, 38.Dupuis, 39.Durante, 40.Durey, 41.Durko, 42.Durufl, 43.Dussek, 44.Dutilleux, 45.Dyson Dates of materials: 1953, 1960, 1970, 1976, 1984
  - Composers E-Em [1953-1981] (Box 37)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Earls, 2.East, Michael, 3.Eaton, John, 4.Eben, 5.Eberlin, 6.Ebner, W. (EMPTY), 7.Eccard, J., 8.Eccles, H., 9.Eccles, J., 10.Edwards, G., 11.Edwards, J., 12.Edwards, L., 13.Edwards, M., 14.Effinger, 15.Egge, 16.Egidius, Magister, 17.Egk, 18.Eichner, 19.Eilenberg, 20.Eimert, 21.Einem, 22.Eisler, 23.Eisma, 24.Eklund, 25.El- Dabh, 26.Ellenstein, 27.Ellis, D., 28.Ellis, M., 29.Ellstein, 30.Eloy, 31.Elston, 32.Elwell, 33.Emmanuel Dates of materials: 1953, 1962, 1971, 1972, 1974, 1981
  - Composers En-Ez [1953-1982] (Box 37)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Encina, 2.Enesco, 3.Engel, 4.England, 5.Englert, 6.English, 7.Enriquez, 8.Ephros, 9.Eppert, 10.Epstein, 11.Erb, Donald, 12.Erickson, 13.Erlebach, 14.Ernst, 15.Escobar, 16.Escot, 17.Esperanca, 18.Etler, 19.Evance, 20.Evangelisti, 21.Evans, G., 22.Evett Dates of materials: 1953, 1961, 1970, 1972, 1982
  - Composers Fa-Fir [1953-1981] (Box 37)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Fabian, 2.Fain, 3.Fairchild, 4.Faith, R., 5.Farberman, 6.Fargo, 7.Farmer, J. (EMPTY), 8.Farnaby, 9.Farquhar, 10.Farrant,11.Farrenc, 12.Farwell, 13.Fasch, 14.Faugues, 15.Fayrfax, 16.Fax, 17.Feliciano, 18.Feld, J., 19.Feldman, M., 20.Felton, 21.Feo, 22.Fernandez, 23.Ferrabosco, 24.Ferrandini, 25.Ferrari, 26.Ferrari, L., 27.Fesca, 28.Fesch, 29.Festa, 30.Fernyhough, 31.Fetler, 32.Feuchtwanger, 33.Fevin, 34.Fiala, George, 35.Fibich, 36.Field, 37.Fielding, 38.Filtz, 39.Finck, 40.Fine, I., 41.Finlayson Dates of materials: 1953, 1975, 1981
  - Composers Fis-For [1965-1981] (Box 37)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Finney, 2.Finzi, 3.Fiocco, 4.Fischer, I., 5.Fischer, J. (EMPTY), 6.Fischer, J.K.F., 7.Fischietti, 8.Fiser, 9.Fish, A., 10.Fisher, W.S., 11.Flagello, 12.Fitelberg, 13.Flanagan, T., 14.Flanagan, W., 15.Fletcher, G., 16.Florest, B., 17.Flotow, 18.Floyd, C., 19.Flugelman, 20.Foertsch, 21.Foggia (EMPTY), 22.Fogliano, 23.Fontana, F., 24.Foote, 25.Ford, T., 26.Formellis, 27.Forrest, E., 28.Forte, 29.Fortner, 30.Forster Dates of materials: 1965, 1967, 1971, 1973, 1981
  - Composers Fos-Fz [1939-1978] (Box 38)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Foster, 2.Fox, 3.Francaix, 4.Franci, 5.Franciscus, Mag., 6.Franck, J.W., 7.Franck, M., 8.Franco, J., 9.Franco of Cologne (c.1250-80) (EMPTY), 10.Francoeur, 11.Frankel, B., 12.Franz, 13.Frauenlob, 14.Fred[erick] the Great, 15.Freed, 16.Freeman, 17.Freschi, 18.Fricker, 19.Frid, 20.Friml, 21.Fritz, 22.Froberger, 23.Froehlich, 24.Frohne, 25.Fromm, H., 26.Frumerie, 27.Fry, 28.Frye, 29.Fuenllana, 30.Fukushima, 31.Fuleihan, 32.Funcke, 33.Furstenberg, 34.Fux, 35.Fu-Yan Dates of materials: 1939, 1965, 1976, 1978
  - Composers Ga-Gh [1953-1984] (Box 38)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Gabriel, 2.Gabrielli, 3.Gaburo, 4.Gade, 5.Gagliano, 6.Gailot, 7.Galilei, 8.Galkin, N.W., 9.Galliard, 10.Galuppi, 11.Galynin, 12.Ganassi, 13.Gandini, 14.Garat, 15.Garcia-Morillo, 16.Gardiner, 17.Gardner, J., 18.Gardner, S., 19.Garinus, 20.Garrida- Lecca, 21.Garth, 22.Gasparini, 23.Gassmann, F., 24.Gassmann, R., 25.Gastoldi, 26.Gataker, 27.Gaultier, 28.Gauthier, 29.Gay, 30.Gedalge, 31.Gehot, 32.Geist, 33.Genet, 34.Gensler, 35.Genzmer, 36.Gerchefski, 37.Gervaise, 38.Gesenway, 39.Ghedini, 40.Ghent, 41.Ghirardello, 42.Ghizeghem Dates of materials: 1953, 1967, 1980, 1984
  - Composers Gia-Gl [1853-1984] (Box 38)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Giannini, 2.Giardini, 3.Gibbons, C., 4.Gibbons, O., 5.Gieseking, 6.Gigault (EMPTY), 7.Gilbert, A., 8.Gilbert, H., 9.Gilchrist, 10.Gilhooley, 11.Giles, 12.Gillier, 13.Gillis, 14.Giordano, 15.Giovanelli (EMPTY), 16.Giovanni da Florence, 17.Giuliani, 18.Gladwin, 19.Glass, 20.Gliere, 21.Globokar Dates of materials: 1953, 1964, 1967, 1972, 1976, 1984
  - Composers Go-Gou [1963-1983] (Box 38)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Godard, 2.Godowsky, 3.Goeb, 4.Goehr, 5.Goepfert, 6.Golabek, 7.Gold, C., 8.Gold, E., 9.Gold, M., 10.Goldberg, 11.Goldman, R.F., 12.Goldmark, K., 13.Goldmark, R., 14.Goldschmidt, 15.Goldstein, M., 16.Golterman, 17.Golub, 18.Gomez, 19.Gomezanda, 20.Gonzalez-Zuleta, 21.Goodall, 22.Goode, 23.Goossen, 24.Goossens, 25.Gorecki, 26.Gossec, 27.Gotovac, 28.Gottschalk, 29.Goudimel Dates of materials: 1963-64, 1970, 1981, 1983
  - Composers Gra-Gz [1953-1985] (Box 39)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Grabovsky, 2.Grahn, 3.Grainger, 4.Grandi, 5.Grasbeck, 6.Graun, C.H., 7.Graun, J.G., 8.Graupner, C., 9.Graupner, J.C.G., 10.Greene, B., 11.Greene, M., 12.Gregoire, 13.Greiter, 14.Grenon, 15.Gretchaninov, 16.Gretry, 17.Griffes, 18.Griffin, 19.Griffiths, 20.Grigny, 21.Grillo, 22.Grillparzer, 23.Grimace, 24.Grofe, 25.Gross, C., 26.Grossim, 27.Gruenberg, 28.Gryo, 29.Guami, 30.Guarnieri, 31.Guenin, 32.Guerrero, 33.Guershing, 34.Guglielmi, 35.Guido dArezzo, 36.Guilain, 37.Guillaume dAmiens, 38.Guillet (EMPTY), 39.Guilmant, 40.Gurlitt, 41.Gurney, 42.Gustavson, 43.Gutche, 44.Gwilt Dates of materials: 1953, 1967, 1971, 1979-1980, 1985
  - Composers Ha-Har [1853-1980] (Box 39)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Haba, 2.Haber, 3.Hacomplaynt, 4.Hadley, H. (EMPTY), 5.Hadley, P., 6.Hadow, 7.Hauhnel, 8.Hageman, 9.Haieff, 10.Hale, 11.Halevy, 12.Halffter, C., 13.Halffter, R., 14.Hall, R., 15.Hallnas, 16.Hamal, 17.Hambraeus, 18.Hamerik, 19.Hamilton, 20.Unlabeled (Hamlisch), 21.Hammerschmidt (EMPTY), 22.Hammond, 23.Hampton, 24.Handl, 25.Handy, J., 26.Handy, W.C., 27.Hanslick, E., 28.Hanus, 29.Harbison, 30.Hargrave, 31.Harris, A., 32.Harris, D., 33.Harris, J., 34.Harrison, 35.Harsanyi, 36.Hartmann, 37.Hartzell Dates of materials: 1953, 1960, 1964, 1969, 1973, 1976, 1980
  - Composers Has-Hew [1913-1979] (Box 39)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Hasse, J.A., 2.Hassler, 3.Haubenstock-Ramati, 4.Haubiel, 5.Hauer, 6.Haufrecht, 7.Hauptmann, 8.Hausmann, V., 9.Havelka, 10.Hawdon, 11.Haydn, M., 12.Hayes, P., 13.Hayes, W., 14.Hayman, 15.Hays, W., 16.Hayton, 17.Headington, 18.Heckman, Don, 19.Hedwall, 20.Heiden, 21.Heider, 22.Heilbut, 23.Heilman, 24.Heinrich, A., 25.Heinrich, A.P., 26.Heinrich, K., 27.Hellermann, 28.Helm, 29.Helmann, A., 30.Helps, 31.Henderson, A., 32.Henderson, R., 33.Hendrickson, 34.Henry VIII, 35.Henry, P., 36.Henschel, 37.Henselt, 38.Herbert, 39.Herder, R., 40.Heredia (EMPTY), 41.Hermanson, 42.Hermanus, 43.Herold, 44.Herrmann, 45.Hertel, 46.Hervelois, 47.Hetu, 48.Hewitt Dates of materials: 1913, 1953, 1962, 1975, 1978, 1979
  - Composers Hi-Hz [1952-1985] (Box 39)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Hibbard, 2.Hidalgo, 3.Higgins, J.B., 4.Hill, E.B., 5.Hill, J., 6.Hiller, Ferd., 7.Hiller, Joh. Adam, 8.Hiller, LeJaren, 9.Hines, Jerome, 10.Hirao, 11.Hirose, 12.Hively, 13.Hoddinot, 14.Hodkinson, 15.Hoeller, 16.Hoffman, R., 17.Hoffmann, E.T.A., 18.Hoffmeister, 19.Hofhaimer, 20.Hogarth, 21.Hoiby, 22.Holborne, 23.Holbrooke, 24.Holewa, 25.Hollander, 26.Holliger, 27.Holloway, 28.Holmboe, 29.Holyoke, 30.Holzbauer, 31.Hommann, 32.Hopkinson (EMPTY), 33.Horovitz, 34.Horvat, 35.Hotteterre, 36.Hovland, 37.Howells, 38.HSU, 39.Hubay, Jeno, 40.Huber, Klaus, 41.Hufschmidt, 42.Huggler, 43.Hugo de Lantins, 44.Hugon, 45.Hull, 46.Humel, 47.Hummel, 48.Humperdinck, 49.Humphrey, 50.Hunter, 51.Husa, 52.Hutcheson, 53.Hyman Dates of materials: 1964, 1966, 1970, 1975, 1980, 1981, 1982
  - Composers I [1962-1981] (Box 40)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ibert, 2.Ichiyanagi, 3.Ifukube, 4.Imbrie, 5.dIndia, 6.dIndy, 7.Ingalls, 8.Ingegneri, M.A., 9.Ipolitov-Ivanov (1859-1935), 10.Ireland, 11.Isaac, H., 12.Ishii, 13.Istvan, 14.Iturriaga Dates of materials: 1962, 1978, 1981
  - Composers J [1959-1982] (Box 40)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Jacobs, 2.Jacopo da Bologna, 3.Jacotin, 4.Jaques-Dalcroze, 5.Jadin, Hyacinthe, 6.Jadin, L., 7.Jannequin, Clement (c.1485-c.1560), 8.Jappart, Johannes (Fl.C. 1500), 9.Jansons, 10.Jarnach, Philipp (1892-), 11.Jarnevelt, Armas (EMPTY), 12.Jaroch, Jiri, 13.Jaubert, 14.Jehannot, 15.Jelic, 16.Jelinek, 17.Jeney, 18.Jenkins, E.T., 19.Jenkins, J., 20.Jenner, C., 21.Jenni, 22.Jeppesen, K., 23.Jimenez, Miguel S. (1910-) (EMPTY) 24.Jirak, 25.Jirasek, 26.Joachim, 27.Joh. Le Grant, 28.Johanson, 29.Johnson, C., 30.Johnson, H., 31.Johnson, Hunter, 32.Johnson, Tom, 33.Jolas, 34.Jolivet, 35.Jommelli, 36.Jones, Daniel, 37.Jones, Robert, 38.Jongen, Joseph, 39.Joplin, 40.Jordan, S., 41.Josephs, 42.Josten, 43.Joubert Dates of materials: 1959, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1969, 1971, 1979, 1982
  - Composers La-Laz [1944-1982] (Box 40)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Labate, 2.Labunski, 3.Laderman, 4.La Grotte, N. da (EMPTY), 5.Lajaren- Hiller, 6.Lajtha, 7.Lalo, 8.Lamb, H., 9.Lamb, J., 10.Lambe, 11.Lambert, C., 12.Lambert, M., 13.Lambro, 14.La Montaine, 15.Lampley, 16.Lampugnani, 17.Lanchberry, 18.Landi, S., 19.Lane, R., 20.Lang, D., 21.Lang, I., 22.Lange, G., 23.Langey, 24.Langford, A., 25.Langlais, 26.Lanier, N., 27.Lanier, S., 28.Lanner, 29.Lantins, A. de (EMPTY), 30.Lantins, H. de, 31.Lapicida, 32.La Plante, 33.Larsson, 34.Latilla, 35.La Torre, 36.Lauer, 37.Lauridsen, 38.Lavista, 39.Lavry, 40.Law, A., 41.Layolle, 42.Layton, 43.Lazarde Dates of materials: 1944, 1963, 1974, 1976, 1982
  - Composers Le-Ler [1961-1984] (Box 40)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Le Baron, 2.Le Begue, 3.Le Camus, 4.Lechner, 5.Leclair, 6.Lecuona, 7.Lee, Noel, 8.Lee, Norm, 9.Leedy, 10.Le Grand, 11.Legrant, G. (EMPTY), 12.Legrant, J., 13.Legrenzi, 14.Lehar, 15.Leibowitz, 16.Leighton, 17.Le Jeune, 18.Lekeu, 19.Leland, 20.Lemarque, 21.Lemoyne, 22.Lennon, J.A., 23.Leo, 24.Leoncavallo, 25.Leonin, 26.Leopold I (EMPTY), 27.Leplin Dates of materials: 1961-62, 1972, 1984
  - Composers Les-Ln [1959-1985] (Box 41)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Lescurel, 2.Lesemann, 3.Lessard, 4.Le Sueur, 5.Lesur, 6.Letelier, 7.Levidis, 8.Levy, E., 9.Levy, M.D., 10.Lewin, 11.Lewkovitch, 12.Liadov, 13.Lidholm, 14.Lie, 15.Liebermann, 16.Lieberson, G., 17.Lieberson, P., 18.Liebert, 19.Liebich, 20.Lifchitz, 21.Lilburn, 22.Lillo, 23.Liljefors, 24.Linde, B., 25.Linley, 26.Lipkin, M., 27.Lis, 28.Litolff, 29.Lloyd Dates of materials: 1959, 1963, 1974, 1984-85
  - Composers Lo-Lz [1963-1984] (Box 41)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Locatelli, 2.Locke, M., 3.Locklair, 4.Lockwood, 5.Loeffler, 6.Loeillet, 7.Loevendle, 8.Loewe, K.G., 9.Logothetis, 10.Logroscino, 11.Lolini, 12.Lolle, 13.Lontin, 14.Lopatnikoff, 15.Lo Presti, 16.Lorenzo da Firenze, 17.Lortzing, 18.Lothrop, 19.Lotti, 20.Loucheur, 21.Lovenskjold, 22.Lucier, 23.Ludwig, 24.Luebeck, 25.Luedeke, 26.Lulinus, 27.Lumbye, 28.Lundborg, 29.Luther, 30.Luzzaschi, 31.Lybbert, 32.Lysenko Dates of materials: 1963-64, 1976, 1981, 1984
  - Composers Ma-Mar [1964-1984] (Box 41)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.MaAyani, 2.MacBride, 3.MacCombie, 4.Macero, 5.Mache, 6.Machover, 7.Maciocchi, 8.Mack, 9.Mackenzie, 10.MacLaren, 11.MacLaurin, 12.MacLean, John, 13.MacMillen, 14.MacNally, 15.Maconchy, 16.Maderna, 17.Mainardi, 18.Maio, 19.Maione, 20.Makris, 21.Malbeke, 22.Malipiero, G.F., 23.Malipiero, R., 24.Malvezzi, 25.Mamangakis, 26.Mamiya, 27.Mamlok, 28.Mancinelli, 29.Mancini, F., 30.Mangs, 31.Manicke, 32.Manney, 33.Mannino, 34.Manziarly, 35.Marais, 36.Marazzoli, 37.Marbecke, 38.Marcello, A., 39.Marcello, B., 40.Markoe, 41.Markov, 42.Marks, 43.Maros, M., 44.Maros, R., 45.Marpurg (EMPTY), 46.Marschner, 47.Marshall, 48.Marshall, I., 49.Marshall, J.P., 50.Martinengo, 51.Martini (EMPTY), 52.Martino, D., 53.Martinon, 54.Martirano, 55.Martucci, 56.Marvin, 57.Mary Dates of materials: 1964, 1980, 1984
  - Composers Mas-Meq [1954-1981] (Box 41)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Mascagni, 2.Maschera, 3.Mason, D.G., 4.Mason, L., 5.Mass, 6.Masters, J., 7.Matsushita, 8.Matteo da Perugia, 9.Mattheson, J., 10.Matthews, W., 11.Matthus, 12.Mauduit (EMPTY), 13.Maw, 14.Maxfield, 15.Maxwell-Davies, 16.Mayuzumi, 17.Mayer, W., 18.Mayr, 19.Mazzocchi, 20.McBride, R., 21.McCabe, 22.McCartney, 23.McCulloh, 24.Unlabeled (McCurry), 25.McDonald, 26.McDonald, H., 27.McGinnis, 28.McLean, B., 29.McPhee, 30.McRae, W., 31.Meadors, 32.Medtner, 33.Meeker, 34.Mehul, 35.Melamet, 36.Melani, 37.Mellers, 38.Mellnas, 39.Menasce, 40.Mendez Dates of materials: 1954, 1962, 1967, 1970, 1979-80, 1981
  - Composers Mer-Mom [1943-1985] (Box 42)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Mercadante, 2.Merikanto, 3.Mersenne, 4.Mertz, 5.Merula, T., 6.Merulo, C., 7.Meyerbeer, 8.Meyerowitz, 9.Meyers, E., 10.Miaskovsky, 11.Michael, D.M., 12.Michael, Ed., 13.Middleton, 14.Mignone, 15.Miki, 16.Milan, L. de, 17.Milano, F. de, 18.Miller, W.B., 19.Mills, C., 20.Mills, S., 21.Milner, 22.Mimaroglu, 23.Mingus (EMPTY), 24.Minkus, 25.Miroshnikov, 26.Mison, 27.Mitchell, J., 28.Mitchell, L., 29.Mitropoulos, 30.Miyoshi, 31.Moeran, 32.Moevs, 33.Molchanov, 34.Mollicone, 35.Molter, 36.Mompou Dates of materials: 1943, 1963-64, 1985
  - Composers Mon-Mz [1964-1986] (Box 42)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Moncayo, 2.Mondonville, 3.Monn, 4.Monsigny, 5.Monte, 6.Montecino, 7.Monteclair, 8.Montemezzi, 9.Montgomery, B., 10.Montgomery, C., 11.Montoya, 12.Moran, R., 13.Moret, 14.Morgan, R.P., 15.Morison, D., 16.Morrill, 17.Morris, J., 18.Morrison, 19.Mortensen, 20.Morthenson, 21.Morton, J.R., 22.Morton, J.R., 23.Morton, R., 24.Moryl, 25.Moscheles, 26.Moss, 27.Moskowski, 28.Mossolov, 29.Mouret, 30.Mouton, Charles, 31.Mouton, Jean, 32.Moyse, 33.Mozart, L., 34.Muczynski, 35.Mudarra, 36.Mueller, P., 37.Mueller, W., 38.Muffat, G., 39.Mulholland, 40.Muller, G.F., 41.Muller, J., 42.Mulliner, 43.Mumford, 44.Mumma, 45.Munakata, 46.Munday (EMPTY), 47.Muradeli, 48.Muradian, 49.Murschhauser (EMPTY), 50.Myrow Dates of materials: 1964, 1981, 1985-86
  - Composers N [1945-1984] (Box 42)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Nabokov, 2.Nagel, 3.Nagy-Farkas, 4.Nanini, 5.Nardini, 6.Narvaez, 7.Nauwach (EMPTY), 8.Naylor, 9.Nancarrow, 10.Natra, 11.Naumann, 12.Near, 13.Nebra, 14.Neefe, 15.Neikrug, 16.Nelson, J.C., 17.Nelson, O., 18.Nelson, R., 19.Nemiroff, 20.Neri, M. (EMPTY), 21.Nero, 22.Nevin, 23.Neuslieder, H., 24.Newell, 25.Newman, A., 26.Newman, T., 27.Nicolai, 28.Nielsen, S., 29.Nigg, 30.Niles, J.J., 31.Nilsson, B., 32.Nilsson, T., 33.Nin, 34.Nin-Culmell, 35.Nivers, 36.Nixon, 37.Noehren, 38.Nono, 39.Nordal, 40.Nordgren, 41.Nordheim, 42.Nordoff, 43.Norgard, 44.Norris, 45.Novak, 46.Novello, 47.Nystroem Dates of materials: 1945, 1963-64, 1973, 1981, 1984
  - Composers O [1962-1984] (Box 42)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Odell, 2.Odingsells, 3.Ohana, 4.OHara, 5.OHorgan, 6.OKeeffe, 7.Olan, 8.Oldenburg, 9.Oldham, 10.Oliveira, 11.Orbon, 12.Orlandini, 13.Ornstein, 14.Orrego- Salas, 15.Unlabeled (Ortiz), 16.Osborne, G., 17.Osborne, W., 18.Osborne, W.M., 19.Otte, 20.Ottman, 21.Oubradous, 22.Overton Dates of materials: 1962, 1981, 1984
  - Composers Pas-Per [1968-1984] (Box 43)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Pasatieri, 2.Pasmore, 3.Pasquini, 4.Passereau, 5.Patterson, P., 6.Patton, 7.Paulli, 8.Paulson, 9.Paulus, 10.Paumann, 11.Paxton, S., 12.Paxton, T., 13.Peaslee, 14.Peck, R., 15.Pedtke, 16.Peebles, 17.Peerson, 18.Pelham, 19.Pellegrini, 20.Peloquin, 21.Pembauer, 22.Penherski, 23.Penn, A., 24.Penn, W., 25.Pepping, 26.Pepusch, 27.Perez, 28.Pergament Dates of materials: 1968, 1973, 1978, 1982, 1984
  - Composers Peri-Ph [1961-1984] (Box 43)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Peri, 2.Unlabeled (Perle), 3.Perotin, 4.Perron, 5.Perry, G., 6.Pert, 7.Perti, 8.Peter, 9.Peterson, J., 10.Petouille, 11.Petrassi, 12.Petrus de Cruce, 13.Pettersson, 14.Pevernage (EMPTY), 15.Pezel, 16.Pfautsch, 17.Pfitzner, 18.Philidor, 19.Philippe de Vitry, 20.Philippot, 21.Philips, P., 22.Phillin, 23.Phillipoctus, 24.Phillips, B., 25.Phillips, E., 26.Phillips, P. Dates of materials: 1961-62, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1984
  - Composers Pi-Pop [1960-1985] (Box 43)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Piatti, 2.Piazzola, 3.Picchi (EMPTY), 4.Piccinini, 5.Picheacute;, 6.Pichl, 7.Picker, 8.Pierneacute;, 9.Piero, 10.Pierre de la Rue, 11.Pijper, 12.Pilkington, 13.Pinkard, 14.Pinkham, 15.Pinto, 16.Pionnier, 17.Pisano, 18.Pisari, 19.Pisendel (EMPTY), 20.Pisk, 21.Pitfield, 22.Pizzetti, 23.P.J. (15th c.), 24.Platti, 25.Pleskow, 26.Pleyel, 27.Plotwell, 28.Plush, 29.Poglietti, 30.Pollarolo, C.F., 31.Pollarolo, G.A. (EMPTY), 32.Ponce, 33.Ponchielli, 34.Poneacute;, 35.Poos, 36.Poot, 37.Popper Dates of materials: 1960, 1970, 1973, 1981, 1985
  - Composers Por-Q [1968-1982] (Box 43)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Porcelijn, 2.Porpora, 3.Porsile, 4.Porter, A., 5.Porter, Q., 6.Porto (EMPTY), 7.Posch, 8.Potter, C., 9.Potter, H., 10.Pound, 11.Pousseur, 12.Powell, J., 13.Powell, Mel, 14.Powell, Mor., 15.Power, 16.Prado, 17.Praetorius, H. (EMPTY), 18.Praetorius, M., 19.Pratt, S., 20.Premru, 21.Previn, 22.Prince, R., 23.Prinz, 24.Pritchard, 25.Proto, 26.Provenzale, 27.Prowo, 28.Puerl (EMPTY), 29.Pugnani, 30.Pujol (EMPTY), 31.Puschmann, 32.Pykini, 33.Quagliati, 34.Quantz, 35.Quinciani (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1968, 1982
  - Composers P-Par [1962-1985] (Box 44)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Pachebel, C.T., 2.Pachebel, J., 3.Pacius, 4.Paderewski, 5.Padovano, 6.Page, N.C., 7.Paik, 8.Paine, 9.Paisiello, 10.Pallavicino, 11.Palmer, Rob., 12.Palmer, Rud., 13.Panetti, 14.Panufnik, 15.Paolo Tenorista, 16.Papineau, 17.Paradisi, 18.Parisien, 19.Parker, H., 20.Parris, 21.Parrott, 22.Parry, 23.Parsley, 24.Parsons, M., 25.Part, 26.Partch, 27.Partos Dates of materials: 1962, 1969, 1979, 1984, 1985
  - Composers Ra-Res [1963-1984] (Box 44)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Rabaud, 2.Rabe, 3.Raeburn, 4.Raff, 5.Rahn, 6.Raison, 7.Ralph, 8.Ramirez, 9.Ramsay, 10.Ramsier, 11.Ran, 12.Randall, Jam., 13.Randall, John, 14.Randulfus, 15.Ranki, 16.Rathaus, 17.Rautavaara, 18.Ravenscroft, 19.Rawsthorne, 20.Raxach, 21.Rayment, 22.Re, 23.Read, 24.Rebel, 25.Reck, 26.Reda, 27.Redford (EMPTY), 28.Regis, 29.Regnart, 30.Reich, 31.Reicha, A., 32.Reicha, J.G., 33.Reichardt, 34.Reiche, 35.Reid, 36.Reimann, 37.Reinagle, 38.Reinecke, 39.Reinhardt, 40.Reinike, 41.Reinken Dates of materials: 1963, 1964, 1979, 1981, 1985
  - Composers Rei-Riz [1965-1979] (Box 44)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Reise, 2.Reusner (EMPTY), 3.Reutter, 4.Revueltas, 5.Reynolds, R., 6.Reznicek, 7.Rezon, 8.Rheinberger, 9.Rhodes, P., 10.Rhodes, T., 11.Richafort, 12.Richter, F.X., 13.Ries, F., 14.Rieti, 15.Rifkin, 16.Righini, 17.Rihm, 18.Riley, E., 19.Riley, T., 20.Ringo, 21.Risager, 22.Risset, 23.Ritter, 24.Rivier Dates of materials: 1965, 1969, 1979
  - Composers Ro-Ros [1960-1984] (Box 44)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Robert, P., 2.Robinson, E., 3.Robinson, T., 4.Rockstro, 5.Rodrigo, 6.Rogers, Ben. (EMPTY), 7.Rogers, Ber., 8.Rogers, J.H., 9.Rohe, 10.Rokeach, 11.Rolnick, 12.Romanini, 13.Romberg, 14.Ronnefeld, 15.Ropartz, 16.Rore, 17.Rosenberg, 18.Rosenmueller, 19.Rosenthal, M., 20.Rosetti, 21.Ross, 22.Rossellini, 23.Rossello (EMPTY), 24.Rosseter, 25.Rossi, L., 26.Rossi, M., 27.Rossi, S. Dates of materials: 1960, 1976, 1984
  - Composers Schi-Ses [1961-1981] (Box 45)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Schikele, 2.Schidlowsky, 3.Schildt (EMPTY), 4.Schlick, 5.Schloeger, 6.Schmeltzl (EMPTY), 7.Schmelzer, 8.Schmid, 9.Schmidt, F., 10.Schmidt, O., 11.Schmitt, 12.Schnabel, 13.Schnitte, 14.Schnittke, 15.Schobert, 16.Schoeck, 17.Schoeffer, 18.Schoenherr, 19.Schollum, 20.Schonbach, 21.Schroder, 22.Schubel, 23.Schuermann, G., 24.Schuermann, G.C., 25.Schul, 26.Schulz (EMPTY), 27.Schulz-Evler, 28.Schwantner, 29.Schwartz, C., 30.Schwartz, E., 31.Schwartz, P., 32.Schwegler, 33.Sciammarella, 34.Scronx, 35.Sculthorpe, 36.Searle, 37.Seawright, 38.Sebastian, 39.Secunda, 40.Sedaka, 41.Seeger, 42.Segerstam, 43.Seiber, 44.Seixas, 45.Selby, 46.Selesses, 47.Seletzky, 48.Selle (EMPTY), 49.Senfl, 50.Serebrier, 51.Serly, 52.Serocki, 53.Serrano, 54.Servais Dates of materials: 1961, 1965, 1975, 1981
  - Composers Set-Si [1963-1981] (Box 45)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Seter, 2.Severac, 3.Sgambati, 4.Shanet, 5.Shankar, 6.Shapero, 7.Shapey, 8.Shareh, 9.Shaughnessy, 10.Shaw, O., 11.Shchedrin, 12.Shebalin, 13.Sheinfeld, 14.Shelbye, 15.Sheppard, 16.Shepherd, 17.Sherman, A., 18.Sherman, G., 19.Sherman, T., 20.Shifman, 21.Shifrin, 22.Shulman, 23.Shure, 24.Sicilianos, 25.Sickelmore, 26.Sickl, 27.Siday, 28.Siebert, 29.Siegmeister, 30.Sigurbjornsson, 31.Silverman, 32.Silvestrov, 33.Simpson, C. (EMPTY), 34.Simpson, R., 35.Singer, A., 36.Singer, L., 37.Singigaglia (EMPTY), 38.Sissle, 39.Sivak Dates of materials: 1963, 1968, 1975, 1981
  - Composers Sj-Spo [1961-1982] (Box 45)